[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
[ GIRLS CHANTING INDISTINCTLY ]
GIRLS [ CHANTING ] : Ours is the power , now is the time
This is the hour , ours is the magic
Ours is the power , now is the time
Ours is the hour , now is the time
Ours is the hour , ours is the magic
Ours is the power
[ OUR LADY PEACE 'S " TOMORROW NEVER KNOWS " PLAYING ]
â  ª Turn off your mind â  ª
â  ª Relax And float down stream â  ª
â  ª It is not dying â  ª
â  ª Lay down all thoughts Surrender to the void â  ª
â  ª It is shining â  ª
â  ª That you may see The meaning of within â  ª
â  ª It is being â  ª
STEWARDESS : Move your seats to the upright position , please .
MR. BAILEY : Come on , let 's go . Come on , darling , taxi 's waiting .
â  ª It is knowing â  ª
â  ª That ignorance and hate May mourn the dead â  ª
â  ª It is believing â  ª
â  ª But listen to the color Of your dreams â  ª
â  ª It is not living â  ª
[ MR. BAILEY SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
Oh , no .
Oh , yeah , it 's a lot drier in here , Dad .
Oh , God . We need a new roof . Yeah .
But it 's big . It 's big .
I like the peg and groove floors .
Damask curtains would look really nice .
Yeah . I gotta get this roof fixed , honey .
Yeah .
â  ª That ignorance and hate â  ª
â  ª May mourn the dead â  ª
â  ª Of the beginning â  ª
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
I found this out back . Do you want it ?
Ah ! Aah !
Relax . What 's the matter with you ? Relax .
Dad !
What ? What is it ? What ? Hey !
Hey ! What the ... ?
Get the hell out of here ! What the hell ?
Sarah , you all right ?
Yeah , I 'm fine . He just surprised me , that 's all .
Yeah , I guess .
Are you sure ? Yeah . I 'm fine .
Dad .
Ah !
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
You could wait . Just until you got a school uniform .
You don 't have to go now . I can 't stay home
and watch daytime TV for the rest of my life .
Why not ? I could .
I just wanna get started and get it over with .
You look good . Good luck , Jenny will pick you up .
I 'll walk . Are you sure ?
Yeah .
[ SPONGE 'S " ALL THIS AND NOTHING " PLAYING ]
[ STUDENTS CHATTERING ]
â  ª I 'll bet you say That you will â  ª
â  ª All of God 's people â  ª
â  ª And all them good people â  ª
â  ª They don 't look like me â  ª
Hey , scary bitch alert .
Oh , God . I thought it was Satan .
Oh , my God . She 's ... She looking ?
Oh , God . Oh , she 's looking . Okay . Find a warm place ...
A safe , warm place .
The almanac says today will bring an arrival of something .
Yeah , wonderful , I 'm getting my rag .
" A new wholeness and with it , a new balance .
Earth , air , water , fire . " Maybe it 's our fourth .
We don 't need a fourth .
Nancy , we need someone to call out the corners :
north , south , east and west .
Four would make a circle . Maybe she can be our fourth .
[ GIRLS LAUGH ]
Come on . I love a woman in uniform .
[ SCHOOL BELL RINGS ]
[ SPEAKS IN FRENCH ]
[ CLASS SPEAKS IN FRENCH ]
[ SPEAKING IN FRENCH ]
[ SPEAKS HALTINGLY IN FRENCH ]
[ ALL CHUCKLE ]
[ SPEAKING IN FRENCH ]
Oh , you mean , did I get laid ?
[ TEACHER SPEAKS IN FRENCH ]
Uh , oui , beaucoup des ... Beaucoup de " laid . "
[ SPEAKS IN FRENCH ]
What is that snail trail over there saying about me ?
MITT : This is L.A. We should be learning Mexican or something .
CHRIS : That would be Spanish , genius .
MITT : Spanish .
[ TEACHER SPEAKING IN FRENCH ]
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ GASPS ]
She 's here .
" She " who ? Someone to be the fourth .
She 's the one .
Are you feeling okay ?
That 's her .
Hey , do you guys mind if I sit with you ?
Because I 'm supposed to find a lab group .
Okay .
No , you ... You can sit here .
Happy ?
What ?
Hi . Hi .
You 're Sarah , right ? Yeah .
Hi , I 'm Chris . Um ...
I just wanted to apologize
for those guys in French . They 're assholes .
You know what they say , you are what you hang with .
Yeah , right .
Wait , did you just call me an asshole ?
You did , didn 't you ? I 'm sorry .
My defenses are up . People here have been really rude to me .
Oh , really ? Who else ?
These three girls . Look behind you .
Don 't stare .
That 's slick . Mm-hm .
CHRIS : Oh , shit .
It 's the Bitches of Eastwick . What ?
Yeah , whatever you do , stay away from them .
Why ?
Well , you see the one on the right ? She 's a major slut .
I mean , I don 't know from experience or anything , but ...
And the one in the middle ,
she 's got these burn scars all over her body .
I haven 't seen them , but friends of mine have .
Anyway , they 're ... No , never mind .
What ? What ?
They 're witches .
Witches .
Well , that 's what people say .
So , what are you doing after school ?
I don 't know . Nothing , I guess .
Really ? Really .
I 'm busy .
Football practice . You can come and watch .
Mmm . Football practice . That is so tempting .
[ LOVE SPIT LOVE 'S " HOW SOON IS NOW ? " PLAYING ]
[ INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE ]
â  ª I am the son And the heir â  ª
[ PLAYERS SHOUTING ]
â  ª Of a shyness That is criminally vulgar â  ª
Sarah . Looking for someone ?
No . No .
Some of these football dicks make their girlfriends
come and watch them practice , as if it 's interesting .
Yeah , like the girlfriend over there . Chris Hooker ?
I don 't even know him .
Nancy 's sorry about what happened in biology .
And she 's mean to everybody , so don 't take it personally .
You 're Nancy ? Ah . She 's Nancy .
I 'm Bonnie and that 's Rochelle .
Hi . I 'm Sarah . Yeah . We know who you are .
Do you wanna go for coffee ? No , I can 't . I gotta get home .
My dad 's waiting for me .
You can make something up . Rochelle 's ditching practice .
He comes on to anything with tits , Sarah .
Except me .
I 'm not watching him .
He spreads disease .
I speak from personal experience .
Run , Chris ! Go long ! Go for the pass , baby .
[ LAUGHS ]
He 's a jerk .
Come on .
So you 're coming , right ? Where are we going ?
Shopping . Come on .
I don 't have any money .
NANCY : We get a five-finger discount .
Five-finger discount .
Sarah , where 'd you live before ?
San Francisco .
Why did you move ? Because it sucks there .
My dad wanted to .
It sucks here too . I know . You need a car here .
You need a car everywhere . What 's up with that ?
I slit my wrists .
Sorry .
What did you do it with ? SARAH : With a kitchen knife .
You even did it the right way .
Yeah .
Punk rock . Let 's go .
ROCHELLE : The " right way " ?
How do you know the right way ?
BONNIE : Shut up , Rochelle .
ROCHELLE : Well , how do you know ?
[ EXOTIC MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS ]
BONNIE [ WHISPERS ] : Sarah .
What ?
[ IN NORMAL VOICE ] Put this in your bag .
No .
Everything in nature steals , you know .
Big animals steal from little ones .
They steal for survival . Besides , I already have a diary .
This is different . You put spells and power thoughts in it ,
and then you don 't let anyone else read it , ever .
Except maybe us .
Here .
You guys are really into all this ?
Sort of .
That 's not for you .
I 'm sorry .
What a beautiful ring . It was your mother 's .
Yeah , it was .
Are you going to pay for those ?
Uh-huh .
You 're not like your friends .
You know how to use candles ?
Yeah . You light the wick .
More than that . Red is for love .
Black ... Actually ...
Why you don 't read that ?
It explains it all . Okay .
Twenty dollars .
You know , I 've never read anything
about this stuff before .
I mean , I don 't follow it .
Maybe you 're a natural witch . Your power comes from within .
BONNIE : Come on , Sarah .
SARAH : You guys , I think I should head home .
BONNIE : Just look straight ahead and keep up .
WOMAN : Please , my baby needs some food .
Uh , I don 't have anything .
Don 't give them money . You 're gonna get nailed .
I don 't have anything . Hey , I know you .
I have another snake for you .
Hey , wait a second . I have to talk to you .
I had a dream about you .
In my dream , you were dead !
I 'm talking to you .
Come back , child . Come back to Jesus .
VAGRANT : Don 't you run away from me !
PRIEST : I am the god of the ...
I know what I 'm talking about . I 'm in touch with the man !
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
Listen to me !
[ SCREAMS ]
Come on , Sarah . Let 's get out of here . Come on .
BONNIE : Whoa !
Oh , my God .
Is anybody back there ? No .
We hit him . It hit him .
The car hit him and we made it happen .
Maybe , maybe not . No , definitely .
I thought to myself , " It 's gonna hit him . "
I thought it too . Well , I thought it too , but ...
Sarah , did you think it ? Yeah .
Then that 's it . Sarah 's the fourth .
North , south , east and west . We can make things happen .
I mean , this is it . This is real .
Shit .
You guys , this is really weird .
I mean , he was after you . He was gonna hurt you , man .
It 's not our fault , I mean ...
You guys , maybe he 'll really listen now .
Who ? Manon .
What 's that ? That 's , like , God ?
No , man invented God . This is older than that .
Do you guys worship the devil ?
[ GIRLS LAUGH ]
NANCY : It 's like God and the devil .
I mean , it 's everything .
It 's the trees , it 's the ground ,
it 's the rocks , it 's the moon .
It 's everything . It 's nature .
If God and the devil were playing football ,
Manon would be the stadium that they played on .
It would be the sun that shone down on them .
So does stuff like tonight happen to you a lot ?
No . Not like that . Other stuff .
Where did you learn it ? I don 't know .
A natural witch .
I hate it . It 's always getting screwed up .
It 's like sometimes I 'll want it to rain
and a pipe will burst in my room and it 'll just get flooded .
[ ALL LAUGH ]
Yeah , right . SARAH : No , really .
Or I 'll want it just to be quiet ,
and I 'll wish for it and wish for it .
And then I 'll go deaf for three days straight .
If you can do that ,
have you ever heard of invoking the spirit ?
No .
That 's when you call him .
Manon .
It 's like ... It 's like you take him into you .
It 's like he fills you .
He takes everything that 's gone wrong in your life
and he makes it all better again .
Nothing makes everything all better again .
Maybe not for you .
Where are you going ?
You guys are freaking me out .
[ NANCY LAUGHS ]
Oh , she 's scared .
Nancy , we need her .
Like a hole in the head .
She 'll be back .
SARAH : What ?
CHRIS : You sounded strange when I called last night .
I didn 't think you 'd come .
SARAH : No , I was just surprised .
CHRIS : Surprised ? SARAH : Yeah .
CHRIS : I thought you 'd be with those girls .
SARAH : What girls ?
CHRIS : Those girls with the weird heads .
SARAH : Weird heads ? CHRIS : Yeah .
SARAH : What 's weird about their heads ?
CHRIS : That one girl , she 's got a mammoth head .
SARAH : Really ?
Yeah . She looks like a St. Bernard .
I haven 't noticed her .
I hate that , that big head thing .
It 's better than that shrunken head thing . Little tiny ...
Makes you wanna hang it from a rear-view mirror .
What 's your obsession with heads ?
Well , I was just noticing how great yours is .
You like my head ? Yeah , it 's a good head .
" It 's a good head . " It 's good .
It 's good for kissing . Can I ?
[ JEWEL 'S " UNDER THE WATER " PLAYING ]
We 'll see you later , bro . Nice meeting you , Sarah .
Yeah , bye . See you .
Come on . Let 's go to my house . Nobody 's there .
I don 't ... I don 't wanna go .
I can 't . I gotta go home .
All right .
Are you mad ?
No .
I 'm sorry .
It 's okay .
So , hot stuff , how did it go ?
How 'd what go ?
Your date with Chris .
What are you talking about ?
Chris already told everybody .
He told everybody what ? That you guys did it .
But we didn 't do it .
Maybe he 's trying to save face then .
Because he 's going around the whole school
saying that you 're the lousiest lay he 's ever had .
And coming from him , that 's pretty bad .
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
No , he didn 't . He did .
He said the same thing about Nancy .
I told you he was a jerk .
Hey .
Can I talk to you for a sec ? Chris ?
I 'm sorry . Chris is really busy .
Maybe we could set something up for ... Nice jacket .
... later in the week .
Why did you lie about me ?
Look , I don 't wanna go out with you again .
Okay ?
Please stop begging . It 's pathetic .
Hey , Chris .
Fuck you .
Nah .
But I will .
She 's gonna cry . And then I 'm gonna cry .
Then we 're all gonna cry .
[ GIRLS CHATTERING ]
LAURA : This is a joke .
I can 't even believe this .
[ GIRLS LAUGHING ]
Oh , wait , here she goes .
Shark !
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
Very good . It was great . Brilliant . Superb .
Oh , God , look . There is a pubic hair in my brush .
Oh , no , wait , wait .
That 's just one of Rochelle 's little nappy hairs .
Why are you doing this to me , Laura ?
Do you think you 're funny ?
You really wanna know why ?
Yes , I really wanna know why .
Because I don 't like Negroids .
Sorry .
I 've told you this before , but I wanna be really clear .
This is a very experimental procedure .
And we can 't make any warranties
regarding results or side effects .
I can tell you unofficially
that there 's little to no risk .
With this form of gene therapy ,
it 's relatively non-invasive .
It can be somewhat painful , but non-invasive .
[ MACHINERY WHIRRS ]
[ KEYBOARD CLACKING ]
[ COMPUTER BEEPING ]
Okay , try to stay relaxed .
I 'm moving the armature over you now .
And you 'll feel a little sting when the needle penetrates .
And then more when the needle moves .
I 'll try and keep it as brief as possible .
Hold very still , but keep breathing .
Okay ?
DOCTOR : Good . Keep your body relaxed .
Ow .
Just a little more , Bonnie .
[ BONNIE GASPING ]
DOCTOR : Don 't move .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
WOMAN : Ray , the light 's out ! Oh , man .
You ... You didn 't even pay the bill . I gave you money .
You didn 't pay the bill . What are you doing home so late ?
You 're late .
It 's the storm , Grace . It 's the connection , Grace .
Oh , it 's a storm ?
That 's why the lights are out , Grace .
GRACE : The neighbor 's lights aren 't out .
I give you money , and you tell me you paid the bill .
But you can 't even pay a bill ? What are you good for ?
RAY : You know what I 'm good for .
Hey , Sarah . We 're going on a field trip .
Miss Downs , I hate to interrupt
your little social gathering .
Sorry , Sister . Yo .
[ LAUGHING ]
[ JULIANA HATFIELD 'S " WITCHES SONG " PLAYING ]
â  ª Shall I see tonight sister â  ª
â  ª Bathed in magic grease â  ª
[ GIRL WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY ]
â  ª Where the two roads meet â  ª
â  ª We will form the circle â  ª
â  ª Hold our hands and chant â  ª
You girls watch out for those weirdoes .
We are the weirdoes , mister .
â  ª Danger is great joy â  ª
â  ª Dark is bright as fire â  ª
[ ALL CHATTERING ]
â  ª Happy is our family â  ª
ALL [ CHANTING ] : Earth , air , fire , water
Earth , air , fire , water
Water , water , water Air , air , air
Earth , air , fire , water ...
It is better that you should rush upon this blade
than enter the circle with fear in your heart .
How do you enter ?
With perfect love and perfect trust .
It is better that you should rush upon this blade
than enter the circle with fear in your heart .
How do you enter ?
With perfect love and perfect trust .
It is better that you should rush upon this blade
than enter the circle with fear in your heart .
How do you enter ?
With perfect love and perfect trust .
That 's a girl .
As above , so below .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
I drink of my sisters ,
and I ask for the ability to not hate those who hate me .
Especially racist pieces of bleached-blond shit
like Laura Lizzie .
Right on .
I drink of my sisters ,
and I ask to love myself more
and to allow myself to be loved more by others .
Especially Chris Hooker . I know , it 's pathetic .
ROCHELLE : Definitely pathetic .
I drink of my sisters ,
and I take into myself the power
to be beautiful outside as well as in .
Bonnie .
[ SIGHS ]
I drink of my sisters ,
and I take into myself ...
all the power of Manon .
That 's all ?
[ ALL CHUCKLE ]
Blessed be .
ALL : Blessed be .
I thought you were gonna burp .
Oh , my God .
What ?
Look .
Oh !
It 's Manon . It 's so beautiful .
He 's listening to us .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ SPEAKS IN FRENCH ]
Do you think it 's working ? I don 't know .
I think he just looked at me . Did he look at me ?
Is he looking ? Not right now , but he just did .
So weird . I know . Now he 's looking .
He 's looking ? Yes .
Shh . Shh .
Is he still back there ? Yep .
Sarah . Yeah ?
Never mind .
It 's working .
That , or he 's gone completely crazy .
You hate me , right ? No .
You don 't ? No .
Because , you see , when you 're a guy , and I am ,
people expect things .
I mean , I know I said some nasty things about you .
Did you tell your friends ? What ?
That you 're a lying sack of shit .
No , but I will .
I 'll tell them tomorrow . I 'll tell the truth .
Good .
Oh , can I sit with you in Mass ?
Yeah , sure .
[ SARAH BONNIE SNICKERING ]
BONNIE : Shh . SARAH : Shh .
[ CHURCH BELLS RINGING ]
[ ORGAN PLAYING SOFTLY ]
[ BOTH GIGGLING ]
Watch this . Ahem .
Chris , could you carry these for me ?
They 're really heavy . Yeah .
Oh , and Bonnie 's too . She 's got a bad back .
And this . Thanks .
[ STUDENTS MURMURING AND LAUGHING ]
Hey , Chris , could you hold my jock for me ?
It 's kind of heavy .
PRIEST : In the book of Genesis ...
What are you , the Stepford boy ?
Sit .
[ STUDENTS MURMURING AND SNICKERING ]
Hello ?
Hey . Pay attention .
[ SNICKERING ]
It 's working . Check it out , her spell is working .
Nancy , oh , my God . Would you look ?
I 'm sorry , I 'm really bad . Get one in already .
Look , it 's hard , you know .
You 're like two feet away from each other .
[ ROCHELLE GRUNTS ]
Get off .
I 'm not that heavy .
Yeah , you 're light as a feather .
During deep space travel .
I am , actually .
Did you guys ever play that game
Light as a Feather , Stiff as a Board ?
Mm-mm . No .
One girl lays down and you surround her
and you put your fingers underneath ...
Put your fingers where ? [ LAUGHS ]
Okay .
Now , you take your index finger and your middle finger
and you put it under her , like this .
Now you have to imagine that she 's incredibly light ,
like she 's made out of air .
Now , is that her whole body , or just her head ?
Cow !
You guys , come on , concentrate or it 's not gonna work .
I think I sprained my finger .
Shut up . Focus .
Come on , you guys . Come on . Ready ?
ALL [ CHANTING ] : Light as a feather Stiff as a board
Light as a feather Stiff as a board
[ CHANTING CONTINUES ]
[ WHISPERS ] Holy shit !
[ GASPS ]
You guys , it 's not working .
Whoa .
Shut up , or you 're gonna fall .
How do I get down ? SARAH : Shh !
[ LAUGHS ]
Who 's got the instructions ?
Just keep concentrating .
Amazing .
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
Hi , I got clean towels for everyone .
Aah ! Oh , my butt !
What 's going on in here ? Nothing . Why ?
Are you girls getting high ? No , Mom .
Are you okay ?
[ LAUGHING ]
You gotta try it .
[ LETTERS TO CLEO 'S " DANGEROUS TYPE " PLAYING ]
â  ª Can I touch you Are you out of touch ? â  ª
â  ª I guess I never Noticed that much â  ª
â  ª Geranium lover I 'm live on your wire â  ª
â  ª Come and take me Whoever you are â  ª
â  ª She 's a lot like you â  ª
â  ª The dangerous type â  ª
â  ª Come on and hold me tight â  ª
[ INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE ]
â  ª Inside angel Always upset â  ª
â  ª Keeps on forgetting That we ever met â  ª
â  ª Can I bring you Out in the light ? â  ª
â  ª My curiosity 's Got me tonight â  ª
Ow ! You pulled my hair out !
Sorry , I thought I saw a bug .
They have shampoo for that , you know .
Stupid bitch .
[ SIOUXSIE THE BANSHEES ' " SICK CHILD " PLAYING ]
SARAH : Ugh . Laura really has split ends .
ROCHELLE : Really ?
I guess this confirms she 's not a natural blond .
Bleach .
What do you think will happen to Laura ?
I don 't know . If she leaves you alone ,
nothing will happen to her . Nothing could .
Fat chance .
Who 's that ?
SARAH : That 's my real mother .
ROCHELLE : Where is she ?
She died when she was having me .
Sorry . It 's okay .
BONNIE : Manon . Take my scars .
Give me beauty outside as well as in .
Manon , take my scars .
Take my scars .
Thank you .
Don 't hit your head on the board !
COACH : Put a lid on it , Laura .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
LAURA : Oh , my God !
GIRL 1 : What 's the matter ? GIRL 2 : Oh , my God .
What happened ? LAURA : I don 't know .
What does it look like ?
[ GIRLS CHATTERING ]
Ew ! Gross !
[ ALL CHATTERING ]
[ SCOFFS ]
Now I want you to remember
that we may need to make several passes
before we can see any results .
Is it better ? I can 't tell yet , dear .
[ CAMERA CLICKING ]
Just a minute .
What does it look like ?
I don 't know . Just wait .
[ ]
I can 't believe it .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
It worked .
What ?
DOCTOR : It worked .
[ GASPS ]
Bonnie .
Seriously , if you don 't stop , you can ... You can go blind .
Hairy palms ?
She was supposed to come back today .
Did you talk to her ? No .
TEACHER : Principal Draper has called a special assembly
during the second half of the fifth period ...
Whoa .
Homeroom starts at 8 : 45 sharp . Sorry , my pedicure ran late .
[ STUDENTS LAUGH ]
ROCHELLE : Bonnie . MITT : Wow .
NANCY : Holy shit . Hi , Bonnie .
How 's it going ?
NANCY : Yeah , how 's it going , Bonnie ?
ROCHELLE : My God .
You look so beautiful . I can 't believe it .
You did it . No , I didn 't do it .
Yeah , you did . I helped .
You totally did it .
Come on , you made Chris love you . You own him .
You made Laura Lizzie 's hair fall out .
You guys should see her . She has to wear a hat every day now .
Poor Laura .
What 's wrong with Nancy ?
Her spell 's not working .
What spell ? I don 't know .
I think she doesn 't wanna be white trash or something .
And I told her , like ,
" You 're white , honey . Just deal with it . "
[ CHANTING INDISTINCTLY ]
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ TIMER BEEPING ]
Okay . Come on , come on , come on .
Ooh , I can almost see through this thing .
Leave me alone !
Jesus . God .
You 're supposed to act like a father to the girl .
Ooh , I ain 't her father . Thank God .
Her father was the one who paid you the $ 50
for a quick bang in the back seat .
Hey .
[ GRACE GASPS ]
Don 't you ever hit me ! Don 't touch her ! Stop !
What the hell is that ? Oh , my God . Oh , God .
You pig .
[ GASPING ]
Ray ?
[ SIREN WAILING ]
O2 's flowing . He 's asystole . We got a flatline .
[ MONITOR BEEPING ]
What 's happening ? What 's happening to him ?
MAN : I know this is a difficult time for you ,
but it is procedure that I ask just a few questions
before we can start processing the policy .
I don 't understand . What policy ?
Mr. Saunders had a whole-life pension plan
through the company . And with benefits this size ,
it 's standard that I ... What size ?
Um ... Just a second here .
Sorry . Uh ...
A hundred and seventy-five thousand dollars .
A hundred ...
Wait , are you saying that this goes to us ?
Five ... To you .
A hundred and seventy-five ... What a dear , sweet man .
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
BOTH : A hundred and seventy-five thousand dollars !
A hundred and seventy-five thousand dollars !
I can 't believe he 's dead . Do you think we killed him ?
No . Not at all .
Hi ! Don 't be shy , honey .
Nice ass . Bonnie .
What ? He has a cute butt . You 're a slut .
Maybe you should go ask him out , Bonnie .
SARAH : Yeah . " I like your butt . Do you wanna have dinner ? "
[ CONNIE FRANCIS ' " FALLIN ' " PLAYING ]
â  ª Like a star Up in the blue â  ª
ALL : Hey !
SARAH : This is nice !
Bedroom , bathroom ... BONNIE : Wow , this is great .
SARAH : Hi there . You look so pretty .
I 'm so glad you could come and see our apartment .
" Our apartment . " We have an apartment .
It is so big . And look at this view . Look at it .
It 's beautiful . Oh , look at the couch .
This is our couch . I love this couch .
I saw it in the window and I said ,
" I have to have this couch . " The guy , what an attitude .
I said , " Honey , wrap it up , I 'll take it right now . "
Cash . Oh , oh , oh !
My jukebox .
[ LAUGHS ]
Every song on here is by Connie Francis .
Yeah , isn 't that great ?
Ever since I was a little girl I said :
All I want in life is a jukebox
that plays nothing but Connie Francis records .
That 's great . Mm-hm .
Who 's Connie Francis ?
Oh , shut up , honey . Listen and learn .
Connie Francis ...
- NANCY : Shall we go to my room , girls ? - Let 's go .
It was nice to see you again , Mrs. Downs .
Connie Francis is ...
Wait a minute here ...
Let 's have a little housewarming party .
Sorry , Mom .
[ GIRLS LAUGH ]
BONNIE : This is cool .
Hey , I was reading and I found something
I think you guys might be into .
" Glamour . Throwing a glamour ,
" an illusion so real as to fool an onlooker ,
is one of the oldest forms of magic . "
I bet you I could do that . You think ?
SARAH [ CHANTING ] : This is to feel
This is to be
Shape and form it
For all to see
By the power of Three times three
As I will it , so shall it be
What ? My eyes are brown .
Oh . They 're usually green .
Ah .
You can do that with contacts .
Yeah , but it 's good . I mean , it suits you .
Subtle , but good .
You want something bigger ?
I want bigger . Bigger . Bigger .
Concentrate , come on .
SARAH : Ready ?
[ ALL LAUGH ]
Wow !
Are you impressed ? Yeah , I 'm impressed .
ROCHELLE : You look like Loni Anderson .
You wanna touch it ? Yeah .
It 's real .
And so much simpler than going to a salon .
NANCY : A really shitty salon . SARAH : Why don 't you try ?
That 's amazing . SARAH : Wait , wait , wait . Watch .
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
Make me blond . NANCY : Me , me , me .
No , no . Make me blond . I don 't think so .
ROCHELLE : Oh , come on ! No way !
Do something to me . Do something to me .
What do you want ? Um ...
I want a smaller ass .
[ ALL LAUGH ]
CHRIS : Sarah !
Sarah !
SARAH : Oh , no . No .
Hey , why didn 't you answer the phone ?
It 's 3 : 00 in the morning , Chris .
Oh , yeah . That 's a good reason .
Hey , you know what I was thinking ?
I was thinking maybe we could move in together .
I don 't think I 'm ready for that
kind of commitment right now .
Oh , shit .
Well , it 's just that , you know , I can 't stop thinking about you .
And I don 't know why , but I think I love you .
And I 've never loved anyone before , except maybe my mom ,
and , well , this little puppy that I had when I was little ...
Shh ! Shh !
I think you should go home , Chris .
No , Sarah , wait , please .
Sarah , please , look .
I don 't know what 's happening to me .
I can 't eat . I can 't sleep .
Uh , can I help you ?
No . Nobody can help me .
[ SOFT SITAR MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
Here again . What can I do for you today ?
We need provisions .
I need to undo a love spell .
When you open a floodgate , how do you undo it ?
If you unleash something with a spell , there is no undoing .
It must run its course .
You should let him suffer .
It 's not for you to judge suffering .
When are we gonna find out what 's behind the curtain ?
Yeah , what are you doing back there , Lirio ?
Hiding all the missing kids from the neighborhood ?
What 's there ? Black magic ?
True magic is neither black nor white .
It 's both because nature is both .
Loving and cruel all at the same time .
The only good or bad is in the heart of the witch .
Life keeps a balance on its own . Do you understand ?
Not really .
Well , then , understand this :
Whatever you send out , you get back times three .
ROCHELLE : Wait , we didn 't read that in any book .
LIRIO : No ?
It 's part of a basic spiritual truth ,
said in many ways , in many faiths :
Do unto others as you would have them do unto you .
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
I wanna buy this book .
You want to invoke the spirit ?
You must be experienced to do this , it 's very dangerous .
Look , lady , I 'm a big girl , okay ?
Now , please just sell me the book .
How much ? Twenty-five .
What do you know ?
I have money .
[ MATTHEW SWEET 'S " DARK SECRET " PLAYING ]
â  ª You are sickened By the weakness â  ª
â  ª Of a heart that 's Filled with fear â  ª
â  ª And if the world Won 't understand you â  ª
â  ª You can make it disappear â  ª
â  ª ' Cause there 's A dark secret â  ª
â  ª Carry with you â  ª
â  ª And deep inside The way you hate them â  ª
SARAH : When things were the worst for me ...
Just before I tried to kill myself .
... I used to hallucinate things .
I 'd close my eyes , and all I would see
were snakes and bugs everywhere .
And then I 'd open them , and they 'd still be there .
They wouldn 't go away .
They 're everywhere .
You know , the serpent is a very powerful being .
You should respect it .
Aren 't you powerful ? Yes , you are .
All right , enough screwing around .
Let 's call the corners , shall we ?
[ CHANTING ] Hail to the guardians of the watchtowers of the east
Powers of air and invention , hear me !
BONNIE : Us . NANCY : Hear us .
Hail to the guardians of the watchtowers of the south
Powers of fire and feeling , hear us !
Hail to the guardians of the watchtowers of the west
Powers of water and intuition , hear us !
Hail to the guardians of the watchtowers of the north
By the powers of mother and earth , hear us !
Aid us in our magical working on this May 's Eve
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
Serpent of old , ruler of deep
Guardian of the bitter sea
Show us your glory
Show us your power
We pray of thee
We invoke thee !
O , sacred one , hear our calls Hear our prayers
Ancient wise one , teach us thy ways
We summon and stir thee !
Lend us your powers Show us your glory
We invoke thee We invoke thee
We invoke thee
Manon ! Fill me !
Is he here ?
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
Did you feel that ?
He blessed me .
I can feel him running through my veins .
He 's still in me .
It 's so amazing .
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
[ NANCY LAUGHS ]
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
Look at this .
It 's so beautiful .
This is a gift .
These are my gifts .
I can feel you in me !
I 'm your daughter now .
He 's everywhere ! He 's in everything !
Listen , all I 'm saying is I think it 's enough already .
I don 't know what 's going on with this .
I 'm completely humiliating Chris
when all I wanted was for him to like me .
And , Bonnie , what 's going on with you ? You used to be nice .
Now you 're completely narcissistic .
Excuse me , but I spent a big chunk of my life
being a monster . And now that I 'm not ,
I 'm having a good time . I 'm sorry if that bothers you .
Hey , can you guys tell me what color that light is ?
SARAH : It 's red .
Doesn 't red mean stop ?
BONNIE : Yeah . Red does mean stop .
[ ALL TOO MUCH 'S " WARNING " PLAYING ON RADIO ]
It 's like what Lirio was talking about ,
throwing things out of balance .
I know you guys think we 're getting what we want now ,
but it 's gonna come back to us threefold .
Ooh . Ha !
Are we actually having a theological conversation here ?
I mean , it 's fun , it 's scary . Who gives a shit ?
BONNIE : Oh , Nancy , we do .
What do you guys think ? They don 't think .
Bitch .
And stop trying to win them over because it won 't work .
I 'm not trying to win them over . You 're paranoid .
I 'm paranoid ? SARAH : Paranoid .
I am not paranoid !
Paranoid .
Will you guys shut up ? [ ALL LAUGH ]
Do you want in , or do you wanna leave the circle ?
Because just tell me right now .
Why does it always have to be that way with you , Nancy ?
Because that 's the way it is .
All I 'm saying is I think you should think .
And I don 't want out .
One of these times , the light 's not gonna be green , Nancy .
Are we scared , Sarah ? Are you scared ? Hm ?
[ TIRES SCREECHING AND HORN HONKING ]
[ ALL SCREAM ]
Whoo !
Nancy !
That was actually pretty close .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
It just keeps falling out .
I don 't understand this .
What did I do to deserve this ?
Laura .
What 's the matter ? What happened ?
I don 't know . It 's okay .
[ LAURA SOBBING ]
I 'm gonna go get somebody , okay ? stay right here .
[ SOBBING ]
CHRIS [ OVER PHONE ] : Sarah , come home , please .
I mean , you look like you need to talk to someone anyways .
How do you know what I look like ?
We 're talking on the phone .
Look , it 's important , okay ? I mean ,
I just need to be alone with you .
I have to see you . I don 't know why but ...
Why are you being this way ? It 's just dinner , come on .
I don 't know . I ...
Please .
Okay , tomorrow night .
Yes ! Yes , yes !
I 'll see you then . Bye .
[ PORTISHEAD 'S " SCORN " PLAYING ]
SARAH : So when I started hanging out with them ,
I was almost relieved .
I didn 't have that many close friends in San Francisco .
It just felt really nice to belong .
I disagree with them once and they turn their backs on me .
That 's not friendship .
Yeah , I know exactly what you mean .
You do ? Yeah . You know , sometimes
it 's like we 're one person , you know what I mean ?
No , I 'm not sure .
[ LAUGHS ]
I 'm not sure either .
That 's so funny . I was just thinking ,
" I have no idea what I 'm talking about . "
Aren 't we supposed to go to a restaurant
or something like that ?
No .
All right . Look , Chris ,
I know you think you feel really intensely ,
but do you ever stop and wonder where it comes from ?
No .
I can 't think , I just feel . It 's weird how it happened .
I just woke up one day and I couldn 't wait to see you .
It 's like that every day .
But now that I have you , I 'm not letting go .
Let 's just stop and think about
what you 're saying here , Chris .
You don 't even know me .
Here , I 'll give you a backrub . I don 't want a backrub .
No , it 'll be nice . I don 't want you to , okay ?
Just let go . Just relax for a second .
Turn around .
I think you should take me home .
No , Sarah , come on . Chris , take me home .
Well , then just hold me , okay ? Let go . Let go .
Just hold me first .
Fine , I 'll walk .
Damn it !
Sarah . No .
Sarah , get back here . Come back here now .
Goddamn it ! Please , Chris ! No !
It 's gonna happen . Lie still . Let go of my arms .
Chris ! Chris , don 't , please . Let go !
[ GRUNTS ]
â  ª I just wanna be a woman â  ª
Sarah !
[ PANTING ]
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
Oh , my God . Sarah , come here .
What happened ? Are you okay ?
You should have seen the look in his eyes .
It was so weird .
They seemed empty , like it wasn 't even him .
Where would he be ?
There 's a party .
At Trey 's .
No , Nancy . Just leave it alone .
Don 't go . You 're not gonna help anything .
I 'm gonna go play .
[ CHATTERING ]
[ SPACEHOG 'S " THE HORROR " PLAYING ]
â  ª Head on a plaque It 's an immediate problem â  ª
I can 't believe she 's here .
Psst . Hey , guys . Nancy Downs is here .
Nancy ?
I 'm here . You 're here .
We 're all here . We 're all here .
â  ª Stupid Cupid â  ª
â  ª You fucked it this time â  ª
Is Sarah with you ?
â  ª So you consult the TV For breakfast and coffee â  ª
â  ª But your TV 's not hungry But that 's okay â  ª
What 's going on ?
Where is she ?
[ SIGHS ]
[ CUP CLATTERS ]
You and me , we 've had some pretty good times together .
If I remember correctly ,
we had some pretty hot times too .
Remember ? I 've been trying to forget .
Forget ?
Forget this ? Stop .
What 's the matter ?
Not in the mood ?
Not to get my dick bitten off .
Now , what makes you think that 's what I wanna do ?
Go away .
[ SOBS ]
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ GIGGLES ]
What the ... ?
Surprise . Sarah ?
Make love to me , Chris .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
We should not be here . Neither should Nancy .
[ ELASTICA 'S " SPASTICA " PLAYING ON STEREO ]
Rochelle .
How 's it going ?
Fine .
Listen .
[ MOANING ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ BLOWS KISS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
You 're a witch !
They were right .
They usually are .
Nancy , come on . Get off the bed . Let 's go .
She 's a witch too , you know . The only reason you 're
in love with her is because she cast a spell on you .
No . Yes . Sad but true .
That 's why I 'm here . To help you forget about her .
What do you care ? Nancy , get off the bed .
Look , you scared the shit out of him .
Thank you very much . Let 's go .
No . He 's gotta pay .
You 're just jealous .
Jealous ? Jealous ?
You don 't even exist to me .
You don 't even exist .
You are nothing .
You are shit .
You don 't exist .
The only way you know how to treat women
is by treating them like whores when you 're the whore !
And that 's gonna stop !
Do you understand ?
Do you understand what I 'm saying ?
I 'm sorry .
He 's sorry ! Oh , he 's sorry ,
he 's sorry , he 's sorry !
He 's sorry ! He 's sorry ! He 's sorry !
Sorry , my ass !
[ NANCY SCREAMING ]
No !
[ BODY THUDS ]
[ GIRL SCREAMS ]
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ SIGHS ]
I didn 't want ... I didn 't want him to get hurt .
I liked him .
I think that he was a good guy underneath it all .
I didn 't know that it 'd go this far .
I didn 't think it could . Honey , come on .
I mean , it 's hard for you . It was an accident . He fell .
Dad , I need to be alone right now , okay ?
Honey , listen ... Don 't touch me .
Everything I touch turns to shit .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ CHANTING ] I bind you from doing harm , Nancy
Harm against other people And harm against yourself
I bind you from doing harm , Nancy
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ LAUGHING ]
Sarah ...
Stop it !
Stop it ! Sarah !
[ SCREAMS ]
[ PANTING ]
[ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
[ SNIFFLING ]
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
There you are . We 've been looking everywhere for you .
Are you okay ? Yeah , I 'm fine .
We heard the police came to your house .
They came to mine too .
Yeah , well , I didn 't tell them anything .
Well , then why do you wanna leave the circle ?
I didn 't say ... You don 't need to say it .
You 're thinking it .
Look , Nancy , people are dead , okay ? Chris and Ray ...
Those were accidents .
NANCY : They deserved it . Says who ?
Says me . And you know it 's true .
Fine , whatever . I 'm out .
Fine . That 's fine .
We don 't really need a fourth anymore , do we , girls ?
No .
Mm-mm .
But if you 're gonna leave the circle ,
you might wanna think about leaving the school .
And maybe the city too . We 're not sure .
Or the planet .
And please don 't do any more spells on me .
I didn 't .
NANCY : You know ,
in the old days ...
if a witch betrayed her coven ...
they would kill her .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
Bye .
Sweet dreams , Sarah .
How have you been sleeping ?
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
Hello ?
Hello !
Yes ?
Hello .
Hi . Um ... What 's wrong ?
Oh , darling , what 's wrong ?
Look , I know that I don 't know you very well or anything ,
but I , um ... I just didn 't know where else to go .
It 's those girls that I always come in here with .
They 're trying to use magic against me .
You don 't understand . They killed people .
And I tried to do a binding , and it didn 't work .
And now it 's like they 're everywhere I turn .
They 're all around me ,
and no matter what I do , they 're still there .
I don 't know what to do .
You don 't understand . She 's inside my dreams .
She knows what 's going on inside my head .
She can read my mind .
Shh .
I 'm so sorry . I just didn 't have anywhere else to go .
Please .
[ WIND GUSTING ]
Come .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
SARAH : What is this ?
This temple is built on a place of power .
Sarah , you have a tremendous light inside you .
More than any witch I 've ever known .
You must not be afraid . I can 't control it .
I always end up hurting somebody .
Do you hear the voice of your mother ?
What about her ?
She 's telling you to be strong .
She was a witch too , of course .
Didn 't you know ?
No .
You can defeat those who challenge you .
But you must surrender yourself to the higher power .
You must invoke the spirit .
But it made Nancy crazy .
She takes it to a dark place .
Don 't be afraid . Invoke him . I can 't .
There is no other way .
[ CHANTING ] Hail to the guardians of the watchtowers of the north
[ RUMBLING ]
It 's Nancy . I can 't stay here .
No , Sarah , stop ! Sarah !
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
Hello ?
Dad ?
Jenny ?
[ PHONE RINGING ]
Hello ?
NANCY : They 're gone .
They flew back to San Francisco .
They thought you ran away back home .
Look , Sarah ,
there 's been an accident , man .
What are you talking about ?
I , uh ...
What ?
It 's been all over the news .
Go look at your TV .
ANNOUNCER [ ON TV ] : Wreckage from the plane was scattered
over a one-mile-square area .
Authorities suspect severe wind shear
may have been responsible for today 's tragedy .
FAA officials have retrieved the black box
and a full investigation is pending .
Once again : Global flight 321
from Los Angeles to San Francisco has crashed
with no survivors . No . No .
More on this story as details become available .
We 'll also be going live with Carla Hale and the ...
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ HISSING ]
[ SQUEAKING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Oh , my ... Oh , my God .
[ GASPS ]
[ YELLS ]
[ RATTLING AND HISSING ]
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Please ... Please stop . Stop it .
Stop it .
Go away , please !
Stop it !
Gotcha ! Aah !
[ LAUGHS ]
God . If I was as pathetic as you are ,
I would have killed myself ages ago .
You should get on with it .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
Where are my dad and Jenny ?
Oh , you 'll be seeing them soon enough .
You 're going to kill yourself tonight , my dear .
No , I 'm not .
[ NANCY CHUCKLES ]
Surprise .
No . NANCY : Really ?
The look in your eyes tells me you might not be so sure .
After all , you have every reason in the world to do it .
I mean , you killed Chris ,
and you killed your mom .
You killed your mom when you were coming out of her .
Now , that is really special .
Even I couldn 't go that low . Bravo .
Stop it , please !
What 's the deal ? Why doesn 't she use magic on us ?
Because she 's weak ! Weak , weak , weak .
Stop , please .
Oh , God , you 're so disgusting .
[ CHANTING ] Now is the end Let her go in peace
GIRLS : Now is the end Let her go in peace
[ CHANTING CONTINUES ]
I didn 't write that . NANCY : Doesn 't matter .
Handwriting still looks the same .
What 's wrong with your scars , Sarah ?
[ LAUGHS ]
It isn 't real .
Then why are you still bleeding ?
Run ! Run back up to your room ,
like the little coward that you are .
She 's so pathetic !
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
Damn it ! Stop !
[ SCREAMS ]
[ NANCY LAUGHING ]
Please , somebody help me . NANCY : " I 'm bleeding . "
Please .
[ SOBBING ]
What did I do ?
Rochelle , go upstairs . See what 's going on .
ROCHELLE : No . This whole thing , it 's just ...
No ?
ROCHELLE : No .
Get your lazy ass up those stairs or I 'll slit your throat !
You 're as dead as she is .
Come on , I 'll go with you . Shit .
[ CHANTING ] Hail to the guardians of the watchtowers of the north
The powers of mother and earth , I invoke thee
I invoke thee
ROCHELLE : Sarah ?
BONNIE : Sarah ?
By the powers of three times three
Make them see , make them see
Bonnie .
[ BONNIE GASPS ]
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
My hair .
It 's coming back times three .
Not again !
What happened ? Where are you going ?
Where are you going ?
[ CHANTING ] Hail to the guardian of the watch ...
Of the watchtowers of the north
MOTHER : Don 't be afraid .
Don 't be afraid . Reach inside yourself .
Reach inside yourself .
[ CHANTING ] Hail to the guardians of the watchtowers of the north
By the powers of mother and earth , I invoke thee
I invoke thee , Manon I invoke thee , Manon
I invoke thee , Manon
I invoke thee
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
Sarah ?
Did I frighten you , Nancy ? I 'm sorry .
What 's going on ? Why aren 't you dead ?
He came to me . Saved me .
Oh , and he wanted me to give you a message :
You 're in deep shit .
He says you 've abused what he 's given you .
And now you 're gonna have to pay the price .
Did he ? He did .
By the way , what happened to Rochelle and Bonnie ?
They rushed out of here without even saying goodbye .
It 's bad manners .
[ HISSING ]
What 's going on ? What is going on ?
Stop it !
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
Oh , relax , it 's only magic .
Now who 's pathetic ?
[ PANTING ]
I know I 'm a little crazy .
I don 't mean to be .
It all got out of hand , and I 'm sorry .
No more games , okay ?
Sarah , I 'm so sorry .
Good .
I 'm gonna go . One thing first .
[ CHANTING ] I bind you , Nancy , from doing harm
Harm against other people or harm against yourself
Wait . I bind you from doing harm
Harm against other people and harm against yourself
Wait .
I bind you , Nancy , from doing harm
Harm against other people And harm against yourself
I bind you ...
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY ]
You bitch , I 'll kill you !
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
I 'll kill you ! I 'll kill you !
[ SARAH SCREAMS ]
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
Where are you ?
Where are you , Sarah ?
[ GROWLS ]
Where are you ?
Tricky . Tricky , tricky , tricky .
Tricky , tricky .
Sarah ?
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
I bind you , Nancy , from doing harm
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
ROCHELLE : Sarah ?
Hi , Sarah . How are you ?
Good . Then again , I can sleep at night so ...
How are you ?
We want to apologize .
We feel really bad about ...
Trying to kill me ?
Yeah .
Honestly , we never thought it would go that far .
Oh , hi , girls . How you doing ?
BOTH : Hi , Mr. Bailey .
Oh , and you know that thing on TV about the plane crash
was just a glamour ?
I mean , it was a practical joke .
Funny .
BONNIE : Sarah , wait .
We were just wondering , do you still have any powers ?
ROCHELLE : Because we don 't .
Sorry .
So if you ever want to just hang out and chant ,
or call the corners ...
Maybe .
Hold your breath until I call .
She probably doesn 't have any powers anyway .
[ â  ªâ  ªâ  ª ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
Be careful .
You don 't wanna end up like Nancy .
[ SCREAMS AND SOBS ]
It 's you . It 's you . He did it . He gave me power .
I can do whatever I want now . I can fly !
I can ... Ow ! Ow ! Ow !
He gave you something , honey .
But it ain 't the power .
But I can fly . I 'm flying . I 'm flying .
I 'm flying . I 'm flying .
Aah !
I can fly . I 'm flying . I 'm fly ...
I 'm flying .
[ HEATHER NOVA 'S " I HAVE THE TOUCH " PLAYING ]
â  ª The time I like Is the rush hour â  ª
â  ª ' Cause I like the rush â  ª
â  ª The pushing of the people â  ª
â  ª I like it ever so much â  ª
â  ª Such a mass of motion â  ª
â  ª I do not know where it goes â  ª
â  ª I move with the movement â  ª
â  ª And I have the touch â  ª
â  ª I 'm waiting for ignition â  ª
â  ª I 'm looking for a spark â  ª
â  ª Any chance collision â  ª
â  ª And I light up in the dark â  ª
â  ª There you stand before me â  ª
â  ª All that fur And all that hair â  ª
â  ª Oh , do I dare ? â  ª
â  ª I have the touch â  ª
â  ª Only , only wanting contact â  ª
â  ª I 'm only Only wanting contact â  ª
â  ª With you â  ª
â  ª Shake those hands â  ª
â  ª And give me the thing I understand â  ª
â  ª Shake hands â  ª
â  ª Any social occasion â  ª
â  ª It 's " Hello How do you do " â  ª
â  ª All those introductions â  ª
â  ª I never miss my cue â  ª
â  ª So before the question â  ª
â  ª So before the doubt â  ª
â  ª My , my hand moves out â  ª
â  ª And I have the touch â  ª
â  ª Only , only wanting contact â  ª
â  ª I 'm only Only wanting contact â  ª
â  ª With you â  ª
â  ª Shake those hands â  ª
â  ª Ah , give me the thing I understand â  ª
â  ª Pull my chin Stroke my hair â  ª
â  ª Scratch my nose Hug my knees â  ª
â  ª Try drink , food , cigarette â  ª
â  ª The tension will not ease â  ª
â  ª I tap my fingers Fold my arms â  ª
â  ª Breathe in deep Cross my legs â  ª
â  ª Shrug my shoulders Stretch my back â  ª
â  ª But nothing seems to please â  ª
â  ª I need contact â  ª
â  ª Nothing seems to please â  ª
â  ª Nothing , nothing , nothing â  ª
â  ª I need contact â  ª